Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Administrative Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records concerning the "Oral histories documenting Yale University women" project (RU 1051) under Florence Minnis, 1972-2010; Accession 2012-A-026
  - Bibliography (printed sources)
    - Women scholars, historical (Beinecke, SML, etc. manuscripts and EPBs [electronically published books?]), 1979, 1990, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Reading lists, 1970-1972, 1997-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Books -- Yale, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Email Correspondence, 2006-2009; 82
    - Use copies, 2006-2009; 5759
  - Film archive and stills
    - Archive
      - MADID (Manuscripts and Archives Digital Images Database), 1894-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Film, 2001-2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - New Yorker cartoons, 1926-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Universities, general
    - Universities and faculty liberalism, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Women, general
    - Contemporary, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - National Women's Hall of Fame, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Equal rights legislation and sex discrimination, 1972-1988, 2003-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Yale history
    - Yale College officers (historical), 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1969-1993, Judy Schiff's timeline, 1981, 2004-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Yale and women
    - Affirmative action
      - Brewster Papers, RU 11, Circa 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Yale Alumni Magazine article, vol. 39, no. 7, 1976 April (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Minorities and affirmative action (how does this relate to women?), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alexander v. Yale, 1977-1980, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Chauncey, Sam, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Co-education, 1892-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - College Masters, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Divinity School, 1952-1958,1972, 1992-1993, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Dwight, Timothy -- Views on education of women, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      General
      From Timothy Dwight 1752-1817 by Charles E. Cunningham.
    - Furniss, E., Yale Graduate School, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Giamatti, Bart, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Helen Hadley Hall Fellows, 1963-1971, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Kabaservice, G., The Guardians, the Griswold-Brewster years, 1992, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Karabel, J., The Chosen, 2001, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Women and Law School, 1971, 1991-2007 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender (LGBT) Studies at Yale, 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Lucinda Foote Committee, 1963, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - May Day 1970 -- Women's participation, 1970-1975, 1993, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Medicine, 1961-2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Mory's, 1970, 1976, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Music at Yale, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Nepotism rules, 1966, 2002-2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Nursing [Yale School of Nursing (YSN)], 2001-2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Office of Education of Women, Final Report, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Political Science Department, 2003-2008 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Schmidt, Benno, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - "Sex Discrimination at Yale", 1971, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Sexual harassment/allegations, 1971-2009 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Yale in late 1960s (era of George W. Bush), 2001 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Spousal hire, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Statistics, Yale, 1971, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Title IX, 1993, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Unions/strikes, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Women at Yale
      - Contemporary information, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Historical background, 1892, 1971-1994, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Women Faculty Forum
      - 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Gender Matters: Women and Yale in Its Third Century, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - "Glorious Women" (associated with Yale), 2007-2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Walking tour, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Women's Studies at Yale, 1974, 1988, 2001, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Yale University Women's Organizations (YUWO, 1965), Circa 1978, 2002-2007 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Yale BREAK (magazine for women at Yale) 1970-1971, Circa 2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Yale -- miscellaneous, 1986-1988, 1998-2007 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Yale Review, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Yale women (deceased)
    - Addams, Jane (1860-1935, social reformer and activist), 1997-2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Dumas, Rhetaugh (d. 2007) (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Murray, Pauli (first African-American woman appointed Law Faculty, 1962-1965), 2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Articles and reports (historical)
    - Women faculty (general)
      - Women in higher education (general), 1929, 1958-2006 (Box 2, Folder 31-33)
      - Science, 1940, 1946, 1970-2009 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
      - Faculty wives, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - University of Pennsylvania Committee on Status of Women, Report, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Notes on Radcliffe Women Graduate Education Report (1956), 2007 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Feminism, 1948, 1970-1989, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Women and Harvard/Ivy Leagues, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Salaries, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Title IX, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Women and medicine, 1970, 1981, 1998-2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Coeducation (not Yale), Circa 2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Arts and Humanities, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Social Sciences (including anthropology), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Women's Studies (general), 1973-2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Articles and reports (current, circa 2000 on) excluding Yale
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - California Institute of Technology (Caltech), 2001 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Case Western Reserve University, Circa 2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Harvard, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1999, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Modern Language Association (MLA), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - University of Pennsylvania, Circa 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Princeton, 2003, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Washington State, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Yale Archives, Manuscripts and Archives (MSSA)
    - MSSA references, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Arts -- MSSA, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Brewster, Kingman, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Coeducation at Yale, archives, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Women and unions, e.g. MS 1313, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Yale Reports on Women and Minorities
      - Synopsis, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Principal only
        - Synopsis of reports relative to Yale women faculty (c. WFF), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - "Women at Yale: A Statistical Profile, 1969-1979, " Office of Institutional Research (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - "Graduate Education for Women at Yale," Bakke, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - Greene report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Peters Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - "Proposal for Affirmative Action Program for Academic Women", 1972 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Arnstein Committee, "Report to the President from the University Committee on the Education of Women", 1974 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Recruitment and appointment of women and minority group faculty, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - Women's Caucus report to Yale Corporation, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Crothers report, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Summary of Yale Affirmative Action Program, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - "Provost's Report on Affirmative Action", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Rodin Report, 1989, "Retention and Recruitment of Minorrity Group Members on the Faculty at Yale", 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - "Jaynes Committee Report", 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - "Women and Yale University: A View from 2002" (WFF) (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Provost's Office
          - Yale Child Care Services, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
          - Faculty Diversity Initiative, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Yale University Records
      These materials are photocopies of selected items from the listed collections. The exact location of the originals (series, box and folder numbers) is recorded on the folders.
      - Kingman Brewster Records (RU 11)
        - Admissions
          - Corporation interest
            - 1965 Feb-1966 Sep, 1966 Jun, August (Box 3, Folder 18)
            - 1966 Apr-Sep (Box 3, Folder 19)
            - 1966 Oct-Nov, 1966 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 20)
          - Policy
            - Undergraduate 1962-1967, 1967 April (Box 3, Folder 21)
            - General 1966 Dec-1967 Jun, 1967 April-June (Box 3, Folder 22)
          - Committee on Freshman Scholarships 1964-1966, 1966 June (Box 3, Folder 23)
          - Women at Yale 1964-1966, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 24)
        - Coeducation week, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - Development board -- Yale, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - Faculty of Arts and Sciences -- Humanities -- Director
          - 1963-1964, "History and the Humanities", Circa 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
          - 1965-1967, Advisory Committee/Marie Borroff, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 28)
        - Humanities Center 1968 -- A. Whitney Griswold Fund, 1968 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
        - Council of Masters 1965 -- List of women at Yale (Box 3, Folder 30)
        - University Council 1970 [3 of 3] -- Letter to parents and alumni re May Day disturbances and responses, 1970 May (Box 3, Folder 31)
        - University Council Committee on Sciences 1966-1967, 1967 May 17 (Box 3, Folder 32)
        - University Council Committee on Yale College 1965 -- Drop-outs at Yale (Box 3, Folder 33)
        - Yale University Committee, Report of the Committee on the Humanities, 1968 March (Box 3, Folder 34)
        - University of Wisconsin Report: Equalizing Opportunity for the Disadvantaged, 1964 August 14 (Box 3, Folder 35)
        - Press release re co-education decision, 1968 November 19 (Box 3, Folder 37)
        - Kingman Brewster's co-education proposal; student letter against. proposal; women at Yale: options; Princeton report (title page), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
        - Women at Yale -- President Brewster's original proposal, 1968 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 39)
        - Woman's College Committee press release with names of committee members, 1967 December 151 (Box 3, Folder 40)
        - Women's College Committee 1968 -- Frankel letter, Boroff (Box 3, Folder 41)
        - Women's Education and Yale, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
        - Arnstein Committee on Education of Women, 1974 July 1 (Box 3, Folder 44)
        - Affirmative action, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
        - Gray, Hannah H., 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
        - Greene report: Committee on the Status of Academic and Professional Women at Yale, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 48)
        - "Grim Professionalism", 1973 December-1974 January (Box 3, Folder 49)
        - Greene report: Committee on the Status of Academic and Professional Women at Yale, responses, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 50)
        - Peters Committee report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 51)
        - Yale Non-Faculty Action Committee, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
        - Affirmative Action 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 54-55)
        - Affirmative Action 1974-1975 [1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 56)
        - "Report on Affirmative Action, July 1972-June 1974" by Jackie Mintz, 1974 October 18 (Box 3, Folder 57)
        - Affirmative Action: Some Indices of Progress in Non-Faculty Employment, Dec. 1974, 1975 September 12 (Box 3, Folder 58)
        - Affirmative Action, J. W. Mintz's final report, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 59)
        - "Statement of [Yale} University's Policies on Recruitment ans Appointment of Women and Minority Group Faculty and Staff", 1975 (Box 3, Folder 60)
        - Freshman Assembly, Charles Taylor, Provost, 1971 September 13 (Box 3, Folder 61)
        - Honorary Degrees 1975-1976 -- letter from Pauli Murray to Kingman Brewster, 1975 July 4 (Box 3, Folder 62)
        - Yale Women's Forum, 1977, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 63)
        - Faculty Affirmative Action Advisory Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 64-65)
        - Committee on Freedom of Expression 1973-1976, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 66)
        - Faculty Advisory Committee on the Recruitment of Women and Minority Faculty 1975-1977, 1976 February 18 (Box 3, Folder 67)
        - Concerned Minority Faculty re Affirmative Action, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 68)
        - Staff Affirmative Action Committee 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Council of Masters (RU 299)
        - Minutes Minutes: 1965, first women elected to colleges, 1965 October 1, December 3 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Yale women (potential interviewees)
    - A-G, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 72-78)
    - Gray, Hanna Holborn -- background, 1973-2009 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - H-P, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 80-88)
    - R-T, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 89-91)
    - U-V, 1972, 1976, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - Y, Circa 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Interviewees
  - Computer files (Box 5)
- Administrative and financial records of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, 1991-2010; Accession 2012-A-061
  - Class of 1884 – FY '09-'10 0032728.00.27547A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Driggs – FY '09-'10 0032728.00.27690A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kahn – FY '09-'10 0032728.00.28180A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Yale Memorabilia – FY '09-'10 0032728.00.29155A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spec. Collections–Archives – FY '09-'10 0032730.00.29407A.xxxxxx.802003, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Spec.Collections-Dept. – FY '09-'10 0032728.00.29407A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Discretionary-Law Library – FY '09-'10 1009137.00.51418A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Library Books – Current – FY '09-'10 0036693.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Library Books (Gifts) – FY '09-'10 0036693.00.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Oral History(Yale)1977-1993–FY '09-10 1039187.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802003, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Oral History-Women @ Yale FY'09-'10 0026914.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - P.Cards FY 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Whitney Family Papers – FY '09-'10 1055685.00.W00612.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Presidential Papers Pre 5/10 FY '09-'10 1039269.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Archives Services – FY '09-'10 0026031.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802003, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Student Time Sheets – FY '09-'10, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - M&P Time Reports – FY '09-'10, 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Student and Casual Payroll Records 08/09, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
  - LSF Notebook, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - LSF Notebook, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - M&A Planning, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Orbis 2: Mini-Cataloging, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Processing Manual, 1999-2011 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Public Services Manual, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Reader/User Database Manual, Undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Records Management Program Department of Manuscripts & Archives, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Security Manual, Undated (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Working Group For an Off-Campus High Efficiency Shelving Facility, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Working Group on Library Shelving, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Working Groups on Off-Campus Shelving, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Bingham Archives – FY '08-'09 0032730.00.29402A.xxxxxx.802003, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Bingham Departmental – FY '08-'09 0032728.00.29403A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1884 – FY '08-'09 0032728.00.27547A.xxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Driggs – FY '08-'09 0032728.00.27690A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Kahn – FY '08-'09 0032728.00.28180A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Yale Memorabilia – FY '08-'09 0032728.00.29155A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Special Collections Departmental FY '08-09 0032728.00.29407A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Architecture-Kelly FY '08-'09 1026113.Kelly.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Architecture-Levis FY '08-'09 0032728.00.56455A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Architecture-Murphy FY '08-'09 0030744.00.18000A.xxxxxx.681027, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Architecture-Nelson FY '08-'09 1026113.GEN.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Artemis-Students FY '08-'09 0032746.00.27402A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Buckley Papers FY '08 – '09 0032728.00.51566A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Bullitt – FY '08-'09 1055461.Bullitt.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Discretionary-Law Library (Emerson) FY '09-'09 1009137.00.51418A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - GLBTQ-General FY '08-'09 1035289.Gen.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Law Library-Capital Campaign FY '08-'09 0032728.00.55221A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Library Books – Gifts FY '08-'09 0036693.00.51577A.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Library Books – Current FY '08-'09 0036693.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Oral History Yale – FY '08-'09 1039187.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802003, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Oral History-Women @ Yale – FY '08-'09 0026914.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Presidential Papers – FY '08-'09 1039269.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Archives Services – FY '08-'09 0026031.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802003, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - E-RECS – FY '08-'09 0032630.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802003, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Fees & Fines – Departmental FY '08-'09 0026031.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Learning Plan – FY '08-'09 1022923.00.0061BX.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Royalties – FY '08-'09 1030266.00.0061BC.xxxxxx.802001, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Budget & Finances P-Card FY '08-'09, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 78-79)
  - Budget & Finances FY '07-'08 2007-2008 Budget, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Budget & Finances – FY '07-'08 Quarterly Budget, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Monthly Transaction Sheets, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Endowment Accounts, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 83-85)
  - Current Use Accounts, 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 86-87)
  - Other Accounts, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 88-90)
  - Box Invoices, 2008-2009 (Box 9, Folder 91-93)
  - Endowment Accounts FY 09-10, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 94-96)
  - Current Use Accounts FY 09-10, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 97-98)
  - Other Accounts FY 09-10, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 99-101)
  - Royalties FY 09-10 1030266.00.0061BXC.xxxxx.802001, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 102)
- University Archives accession records, 2009-2011; Accession 2012-A-065
  Restricted until January 1, 2046.
  - 19ND-A-507 - 19ND-A-508 (Box 1)
  - 2009-A-051 - 2010-A-088 (Box 1)
  - 2010-A-089 - 2011-A-066 (Box 2)
- Financial records of the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, 2010-2011; Accession 2013-A-015
  The records for accession 2013-A-015 are restricted until January 1, 2046.
  The dates of the records for accession 2013-A-015 are for the fiscal year 2010-2011 unless otherwise specified.
  - Account files
    - Class of 1884 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Driggs (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Kahn (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Lindbergh (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Yale Memorabilia (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Special Collections - Departmental (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Architecture - Nelson (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Library books - General (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Library books - Gifts (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Oral history - Yale (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - P-card (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Presidential Papers - Brewster (pre-5/10) (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Presidential Papers - Brewster (post-5/10) (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Whitney Family Papers (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Archives Services (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Fees and Fines - Departmental (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Special Collections - Archives (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Learning Plan (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Public Services - Sales Tax Reports (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Public Services - Deposits: Visa/MC (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Public Services - Amex (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Public Services - Vendor Services (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Public Services - Weekly Deposits (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Student Payroll (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Professional Travel (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Royalties (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Position Plans and Consolidated Transaction Sheets - Monthly Reports
    - Bingham Archives (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bingham Departmental (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Class of 1884 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Driggs (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Kahn (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Lindbergh (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Seymour (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Library Special Collections - Archives (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Library Special Collections - Departmental (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Yale Memorabilia (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Monthly Summary - Archives (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Monthly Summary - Departmental (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Sales Tax Reports (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Architecture - Dudley (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Architecture - Levis (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Architecture - Nelson (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Artemis - Students (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Buckley Papers (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Discretionary Law Library (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - LGBTQ - General (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Law Library Capital Campaign (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Library Books - Gifts (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Library Books - Current (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Oral History/Yale 1977-1993 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Oral History/Women@Yale (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Presidential Papers - pre (5/10) (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Presidential Papers - post (5/10) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Whitney Family Papers (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Archives Services (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Electronic Records (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Fees and Fines - Departmental (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - General Account - Departmental (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Learning Plan (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Public Services (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Publications (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Royalties (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Kissinger Project Archivist, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Richard V. Szary, head of Manuscripts and Archives, Records, 1974-2007; Accession 2013-A-022
  Restricted until January 1, 2042.
  - Notes
    - Notes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Notes, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Research services, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Yale University Library, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Video Archive of Holocaust Testimonies, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Notes, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General
    - Administration-meetings University Librarian, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Administration-Valerie Hanson and Lisa Wilson, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Departmental Organization
    - Responsibilities and Structure, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Strategic Planning
    - Administrative planning strategic planning, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Strategic planning-background, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Strategic planning-consultants Winthrop, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Strategic planning-consultants Yakel, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Strategic planning-guests, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)